<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Desser Droid</string>

    <string name="sample_content">Sample of dragging the content.\nThe menu consists of a ListView, for which the
        active position is saved through configuration changes.\nAdditionally, if the menu is open, a back press will
        close it.
    </string>

    <string name="sample_window">Sample of dragging the entire window.\nThe menu is a simple ScrollView, with a click
        listener set on each item.\nThe drawer will animate slightly open, to make it more discoverable.\nAdditionally,
        if the menu is open, a back press will close it.
    </string>

    <string name="sample_listactivity">Sample of how to use the drawer with ListActivity.\nWhen running on ICS or
        greater, the ActionBar up button will blink until clicked by the user. This is done to make the menu more
        discoverable.\nAdditionally, if the menu is open, a back press will close it.
    </string>

    <string name="sample_rightmenu">This sample shows how to position the menu to the right of the content.\nRun on
        an API14+ device to see how it interacts with the overflow button.
    </string>

    <string name="sample_topmenu">This sample shows how to position the menu above the content.</string>

    <string name="sample_bottommenu">This sample shows how to position the menu below the content.</string>

    <string name="sample_layout">This sample shows how to use the drawer in a layout file.
        \nThe top drawer is used in this sample.
    </string>

    <string name="sample_static">This sample shows how to attach a drawer that is always visible.</string>

	<string name="yema_cake">Ingredients : 1 cup rice, uncooked &#189; cup mongo sugar water oil, for deep frying Cooking Procedures : Soak rice overnight in water, then grind.  Wrap in cheesecloth and hang to drip.  On the other hand, boil mongo and mash. Dissolve &#8531; cup sugar in 1/8 cupwater, then add mixture to mashed mongo.</string>
    <string name="sinukmani">This version of Maruya is one that I usually buy for my merienda when I was in the Philippines. I sometimes buy them in a bamboo stick or in a hand fan shape coated with sugar. But their where times that after siesta, my mom will cook us maruya in our merienda before playing outside during summer time.</string>
    <string name="lechetin">Ingredients : 1 cup glutinous rice flour &#189; cup dried tapioca pearls 2-&#189; cups coconut milk 10 cups water 2-&#189; cups sweet potato, peeled and cubed 1 cup sugar 3 ripe saba (plantain) bananas, sliced into rounds 5 fresh or canned jackfruit, cut into strips Cooking </string>
    <string name="cathedral_window">Ingredients : 1-&#188; cups water &#190; cup brown sugar 1 cup flour 1 tsp. lye (lihiya) water, for cooking grated fresh coconut Cooking Procedures : Bring water and sugar to a boil. Let cool. Add to flour, stir until smooth. Add lye water (lihiya) and mix well.</string>
    
</resources>
